A case from the store that never opened,
I set up a little shop you see,
then I said,
Caraca Malandro,
how am i going to sell my clothes,
stand out in the middle of a
so many other stores already more structured
and me in that little door,
a rent of five hundred reais.
I need to make a differential,
I need to use my lighting,
everyone when they open a business
makes opening cocktail,
everyone discloses this yes.
So what did I do in the window?
I put an MDF in the back to cover the inside of the store
and I only put 1 seat,
1 statue of 1 dog,
1 luxury and 1 glass of whiskey,
nothing else.
It was all filmed
and i put the name of bronx store
and then there was only one slogan,
is The boss wantsucy,
the boss wants to see you,
damn it!
It's this slogan
and that there
and then the crowd passed through the center,
didn't understand anything.
What is it?
What is this there?
What is the strategy
so that I can now place a customer inside this store?
There was a kid in the neighborhood who was Luquinha,
ten year old girl.
We took an old bicycle,
we put on a kid in a newsboy outfit,
then we take Luquinha,
we got a bunch of newspaper,
stopped one Saveiro
near the one in the bars across town
and I spoke like this,
to the Luquinha,
that's Estevão
you're sitting there talking red over there,
Or go there,
give him that newspaper,
speak.
That the boss wants to see you and walks out
then you imagine having a beer with your friends there
glue the kid it turns like this
the little boy like that in a beret?
Does the boss want to see you?
Hand over a newspaper and go outside.
And I did it there,
the kid,
the guy didn't understand anything.
I looked there.
Bronx,
closed the doors.
Pow Harris Street,
number three hundred center
the other day,
Jordan,
well, good morning,
I was at a party here yesterday,
man,
a little boy in a beret arrived here,
left me a newspaper,
the boss wants to see you?
I'm not understanding anything.
What is this there?
I
I chose the customers.
The stop is as follows,
you were invited to a VIP Club.
There's how you came there on Tuesday,
two and a half?
Po,
how was I invited?
Then it already gave what?
Exclusiveness?
Two and a half,
guy would arrive at the store.
What strategy did I make?
I used to log on to Facebook before.
Did you know who Estevão was?
Did you know the kind of clothes Estevão wanted?
I set up the entire store with a taste of the Esteban.
When the guy arrived at the store,
po,
does he like what rock?
Man,
I was playing his rock band on screen.
And I don't even like rock.
Three o'clock in the afternoon,
Marcelo arrived.
Marcelo was all ironed up,
with more social clothing.
It changed the entire configuration of the store,
placed the sertanejo,
classic funk music,
it doesn't matter,
I brought a.
Best possible experience with what I had.
As a result,
Jordan bombed,
Brother,
successfully bombed the business.
There were people here calling,
wanting such,
he spoke,
he can only by invitation.
Then I gave exclusivity,
I delivered the invitation.
It was a little boy,
it was the kid.
And that. doubt,
takes, sure,
backs up.
It's over.